Faculty Reference; Collection ua950.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Cummings John Carey, Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 70)
- Cummings, Paul A., Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 71)
- Cundy, Donald, Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 72)
- Cunninghan, Richard P., Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 73)
- Cunningham, Veronica, 1992 (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 74)
- Cupoli, Ed, Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 75)
- Curry, Deborah, 1989-1995 (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 76)
- Curtis, Thomas E, Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 77)
- Curtis, Thomas E, Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 78)
- Cushman, Donald P., Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 79)
- Cusick, Roger, Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 80)
- Cutler, Gary, Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 81)
- Cutler, Gary, Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 82)
- Cuttler, Brian, Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 83)
- Czapski, Ulrich, Undated (Box 8 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 84)
- Dabrowski, Romuald, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- D'ambra, Thomas, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- D'Andrea, Frank, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Daims, Diva Barachini, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Dale, Mark, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Daly, Lawrence Henry, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Dalton, Mark, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- D'Amello, Joseph, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Damhof, Sandra, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Dandridge, Thomas C., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Danese, Gino, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Daniel, Betty C., Undated (Folder 12)
- Daniel, Charles E., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Daniels, Mina H., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Daniels, Thomas, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Danielson, Lucig, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Cummings-Danson, Gail, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Dapo, Donald, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Darbyshire, Sue, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Das, Tara P., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Dascher, Alfred, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Dascal, Neal, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- D'attilo, Michael, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Davidson, Justine A., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Davidowicz, Lucy, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Davis, Edward D., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Davis, Liane, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Davis, Lydia, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Davis, Phillip, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Dawes, Sharon, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Day, Stephen, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Dean, D.E., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Deane, Glenn, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Dear, Gary, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Dearstyne, Bruce William, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- DeBlasi, Anthony, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Decker, Sidney, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Decker, Walter Cornell, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Dedrick, Blanchard, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- deGonzague, Arleen, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Dehais, Richard J., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Deiber, Gwen, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Deininger, Richard C., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- De La Foret, Peggy, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- DeLaMater, Christine, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- DeLamater, Claudette R., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Delano, John, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Delano, John, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- D'elia, Christopher, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Dehong, Dennis, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Delong, Stephen, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Delio, Vincent, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- DelAanto, John H., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Deluca, Nicholas, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Demacario, Everly Conway, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Dembowski, Frederick L., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Demerjian, Kenneth L., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- DeMeo, Joseph, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Debeneaux, Gregory, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Dennis, Livia, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Dennis, Margaret A., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Denton, Nancy, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- De Pasquale, Brian, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Derrick, Virginia J., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 64)
- Derrick, William, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 65)
- Derringh, Edward, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 66)
- DeSantis, Deiedre, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 67)
- DeSantis, Deiedre, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 68)
- Desfosses, Helen, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 69)
- Desfosses, Helen, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 70)
- De Sole, Gloria, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 71)
- Dunn, Daniel, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 72)
- Devane, Mary Anne, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 73)
- Dewey, John F., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 74)
- Dewey, John N., Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 75)
- Dewitt-Parker, Joyce, Undated (Box 9 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 76)
- Diamond, William M., 1969 (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Dickey, James M., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Dickinson, Joanne, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Didier, Maureen C., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- DiDionna, Michelle, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Dieffenback, Bruce, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Gigiorgio, Diane, 1980 (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Dillon, Harold Joseph, 1965-1974 (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Dineen, Richard, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Dinovo, Robert, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Dirocco-Ruskin, Valerie, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- DiSteffano, Jacqeline S., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- DoBell, Howard, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Dobson, Michael W., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Docksai, Ronald F., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Doellefeld, James Patrick, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Doellefeld, Steven F., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Doherty, Marijo (also Norman Bauman), Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Dolan, Donna R., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Doll, Carol A., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Doman, Mary Gay, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Domaracki, Jane, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Donahue, John, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Donley, Donald T., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Donovan, Robert Alan, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Donovan, Robert, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Doolen, Kevin, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Dorfman, Debrah, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Doty, David, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Dougherty, Mary Jo, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Douglas, Gertrude E., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Downey, Shirley, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Dowse, Patricia, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Doyle, Daniel E., 1997 (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Doyle, Kmberly, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Dozier, Cheryl, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Drescher, Nuala McGann, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Dressner, Richard B., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Drewer, Lois, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Driscoll, E. Gallagher, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Drotar, David Lee, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Bangert-Drowns, Robert L., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Duarte, Francisco, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Duch, Raymond, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Duchessi, Peter J., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Dudek, Bruce C., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Dudek, Mairin E., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Dudo, Peter J., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Duffee, David E., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Dukes, Jerome E., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Dulak, Norman C., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Dulay, Heidi, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Dumbleton, William A., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Dunn, Anita, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Dunsmore, Lai Lonnie, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Dunz, Karl, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Dupuis, Barbara, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- Dutkiewicz, Vincent, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Dutta, Savarav, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Duval-Spillane, Pat, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Dwyer, Catharine M., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Dwyer, Catharine M., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- Dwyer, John M., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Dwyer, Thomas, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 64)
- Eadon, George, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 65)
- Dyksta, Robert, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 66)
- Eames, Harriet, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 67)
- Earl, Theodore R., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 68)
- Earleywine, Mitchell, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 69)
- Ebert, Teresa L., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 70)
- Eccelston, Ava, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 71)
- Eckstein, Jerome, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 72)
- Eckstein, Jerome, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 73)
- Edleman, Martin, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 74)
- Edleman, Martin, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 75)
- Edleman, Robert, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 76)
- Edleson, Ivan, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 77)
- Edleson, Ivan, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 78)
- Edelson, Jeffrey, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 79)
- Edelstein, Philip, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 80)
- Edoho, Edoho Bassey, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 81)
- Edwards, Charles, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 82)
- Edwards, Charles, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 83)
- Edwards, David L., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 84)
- Edwards, Richard L., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 85)
- Egelston, Martha Albright, 1929-1973 (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 86)
- Egelston, Richard, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 87)
- Eisenberger, Robert, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 88)
- Ekrich, Arthur A., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 89)
- Elam, Helen, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 90)
- Elbow, Matthew H., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 91)
- Elk, Roy, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 92)
- Elkin, Dennis, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 93)
- Ellinwood, Dewitt, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 94)
- Ellinwood Jr., Dewitt Clinton, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 95)
- Ellis, Beverly, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 96)
- Ellis, Clifford, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 97)
- Ellis, Martin H., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 98)
- Ellis, Michael, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 99)
- Ellis, G.Randall, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 100)
- Ellis, Randall, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 101)
- Ellis, Richard D., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 102)
- Elliston, Frederick, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 103)
- Else, Meinda Sue (Ross), Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 104)
- Elter, John F., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 105)
- Emerson, Patricia R., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 106)
- Emery, James, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 107)
- Empie, KarenEngstron, Mary J., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 108)
- Emrich, Robert L., Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 109)
- Endicott, William, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 110)
- Ennis, Paula, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 111)
- Ennis, Paula, Undated (Box 10 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 112)
- Ensel, Walter M., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Eparo, Philip, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Erie, Stephen P., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Erkes, Joseph, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Erlich, Frederick, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Eson, Morris, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Esperson, James P., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Esposito, Wayne, 1979 (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Estey, Charles G., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Etcheverry, Roland, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Ether, John A., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Etheredge, Lloyd S., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Eubanks, Virginia, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Evans, Aden, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Evans, Carol N., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Evans, Nancy, 1997 July 30 (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Evans, Susan T., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Ezquerra de Alvar, Elena, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Fachard, Denis, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Fadale, LaVerne, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Faerman, Sue, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Fahey, Valerie, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Fairbank, Roswell Evan, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Fairbanks, Robert M., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Fairbanks, Robert M., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Falbe, Cecilia, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Falconer, Raymond E., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Falk, Dean, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Falk, Dean, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Falk, Dean, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Falls, Douglas L., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Fama, Michael M., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Fancher, Michael M., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Farina, Chris, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Farley, John J., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Farmer, J. Walter, 1928-1989 (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Farnworth, Margaret, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Farnsworth, Alton U, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Farr, Daniel, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Farrell, Cathy, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Farrell, Hazel, 1972 (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Farrell, Lawrence, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Farrell, Laurence, 1903-1989 (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Farrell, Margaret A., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Faureau, Donald, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Faureau, Donald, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Federighi, Francis D., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Fee, Ruth F., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Feeney, JoAnne, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Feeser, Patricia, Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Feister, William J., Undated (Box 11 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Feldman, Laurie, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Feldman, Liza, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Feldman, Jerry, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Felson, Richard Barnet, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Felter, Catherine, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Feltsman, Vladmir, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Femminella, Francis, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Fenlon, Mark W., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Fenner, Frank, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Fenton, William N., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Ferdman, Bernardo, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Ferguson, Henry, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Ferlo, Patrick, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Fernandez, Dulce, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Fernandez, Frank L., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Fernandez, Xavier, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Ferrara, Donna, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Ferretti, Lisa A., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Fessler, Susanna, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Fetrow, Jacqelyn, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Fetterly, Judith, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Fetterly, Judith, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Fields, Emmett, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Fields, Emmett B., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Fields, Emmett B., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Fields, Emmett B., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Fields, Emmett B., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Fields, Lanny, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Fieldsteel, Adam, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Fiess, Mary, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Figge, James, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Fillipone, Julia, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Finder, Morris, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Finet, Julia, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Fink, Robert Orwill, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Finkelstein, Alfred P., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Finnegan, Daniel, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Fischer, Philip J., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Fischer, Sandra K., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Fischer, Steve, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Fisher, Charles G., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Fisher, Charles L., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Fisher, Ingrid, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Fisher, Patricia A.P., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Fiser, Webb Sackett, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Fishman, Harvey M., Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Fisk, John, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Fitch, Martha, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Fitzdam, Deb, Undated (Box 12 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)